<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spencer Leslie</title>
    <link>https://scleslie.github.io/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Spencer Leslie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 15:41:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://scleslie.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://scleslie.github.io/blog/resume/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 15:41:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scleslie.github.io/blog/resume/resume/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customer Service Representative with Parker Staffing at Nintendo, Feburary 2017-Present&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I help consumers of Nintendo products in troubleshooting issues such as error code and network problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Account Executive with Colonial Life, May 2016-September 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Colonial Life at the time when I joined had just open a new territory in Northern Colorado, as of now I do not believe it is still active as I left when it was about to be disolved. I was tasked with seeking out potential prospects and managed my own schedule. I implemented social media strategies using LinkedIn and Twitter to increase my potential clientele.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intern at Higgin&amp;rsquo;s Life and Pensions June 2014-August 2014&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal assistant for the President of the company in Dublin, Ireland. Maintaned and updated their Microsoft Access database, conducted phone calls and set up appointments for existing clients, and shodowed meetings with clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head Macinist at Atoc Inc&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fabricated and machined aluminim and sometime steel parts for specialty bike racks. I also assembled the racks, packaged the racks, and arranged shipping orders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Volunteer Work&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;100+ hours at the Fort Collins Bike Co-Op as a Work Night Leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Colorado State University
Bachelor of Arts: Economics with Philosophy Minor&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More coming soon</title>
      <link>https://scleslie.github.io/blog/projects/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 12:00:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scleslie.github.io/blog/projects/projects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I will try to keep a record of what projects I have going on in my life at the time here as best as I can. This includes both professional and personal projects (such as this blog). I will start a post for each project and update them as things progress.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://scleslie.github.io/blog/posts/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 10:45:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scleslie.github.io/blog/posts/about-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Spencer Leslie and I am going to start blogging about the things that I enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>